minecraft-server.net 2018-11-27

# Privacy Policy | Minecraft Servers | Best Minecraft Server List

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on http://minecraft-server.net, place an order and/or when you vote for a minecraft server on this web site.

When registering on http://minecraft-server.net, as appropriate, you will be asked to enter your: e-mail address. You may, however, visit http://minecraft-server.net anonymously. When placing an order we will require your name and address. For European costumers that represent a company we may also require a valid Business name, Registration number and VAT before placing an order. When voting for a minecraft server on http://minecraft-server.net we may collect your entered minecraft username (for Votifer purposes) and IP address to prevent double-voting and also to validate your vote. 

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:   
• To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).  
• To improve Minecraft-Server.net (we continually strive to improve http://minecraft-server.net offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).  
• To prevent booting or any kind of ways to cheat the voting system.  
• To improve our customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).  
• To process transactions (such as payments for additional services).  
• At the point when an end-user wishes to make a payment, his registration details may be passed to Paymentwall that provides payment processing services, in order for Paymentwall to better protect service and end-users from unauthorized payments

• Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.  
• To send periodic emails (the email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order).

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business. Special situations may require disclosure of your data.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies only to save your login preferences for future visits and to prevent booting and voting cheats. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website and/or minecraft server. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. We at http://minecraft-server.net use tools such as (but not limited too) Google Analytics, Google Webmasters and Google Adsense to help improve the experience and maintain our service.

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings. (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)

http://minecraft-server.net (and any sub domains) uses a third party protection service offered by Cloudflare. This service may place cookies on the browsers in order to track malicious visitors, to reduce the chance of blocking legitimate users, and to provide customized services. The __cfduid cookie by Cloudflare is used to override any security restrictions based on the IP address the visitor is coming from. If you do not want CloudFlare to use cookies, you can disable them within your browser. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating http://minecraft-server.net, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on http://minecraft-server.net. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through http://minecraft-server.net and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using and accessing http://minecraft-server.net website, you consent to our privacy policy.

Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on http://minecraft-server.net or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email, notification or text.   
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please [ Contact Us](https://minecraft-server.net/contact/)

**Last Edit : 14th October 2015**
